Guide to the J. Walter Thompson Company. Harry Clark Papers, 1945-1992 and undated RL.00695
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
J. Walter Thompson Company. Harry Clark papers
1945-1992 and undated
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
J. Walter Thompson Company
RL.00695
16.85 Linear Feet
Founded in 1864, the J. Walter Thompson Company (JWT) is one of the largest and oldest enduring advertising agencies in the United States. Harry Clark was an advertising executive who served as Director of JWT's Frankfurt Office and eventually of JWT's New York Office; Managing Director of Landsdowne Advertising, a JWT subsidiary; and co-founder of Smith Clark Associates, a consulting firm based in Princeton, N.J. The Harry Clark Papers cover the years 1945-1992, with the bulk of materials dating from the 1970s, the period during which Clark served as Director of the JWT Frankfurt Office, and during 1984-1986, when he served as Director of JWT in New York. The collection primarily consists of correspondence, administrative forms, presentations, speeches, meeting files, proofs, and financial reports, with extensive records from the Frankfurt Office. Companies represented include Braun, Chevron, De Beers, Eastman Kodak Company, Kellogg Company, Pan American Airways, PepsiCo, Rustenburg Platinum Mines, and Unilever. Acquired as part of the John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History.
12,640 Items
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research.
However, original audiovisual materials are closed to researchers until Use Copies can be produced.
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
All or portions of this collection may be housed off-site in Duke University's Library Service Center. The library may require up to 48 hours to retrieve these materials for research use.
Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library to use this collection.
Provenance
The J. Walter Thompson Company. Harry Clark Papers were received by the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library as gifts in 1987 and 1993.
Biographical Note
Chronology
1935, Sept. 5 Born Harold Frank Clark, Jr., Norwalk, Conn.
1957 BA, Amherst College, Amherst, Mass.
1957-1959 MA, English Literature, Stanford University
1959 International Representative, JWT New York Office
1965 Account Supervisor, JWT Frankfurt Office
1967 PhD, English Literature, Columbia University; dissertation titled Dickensian Journalism: A Study in Household Words
1969 Director, JWT Frankfurt Office
1970 Managing Director, JWT Frankfurt Office; Management Supervisor on major accounts
1974 Senior Vice President of JWT, relocated to New York
1977 Group Account Director on Labatts, Reader's Digest and, in 1979, Burger King accounts
1983 Managing Director, Landsdowne Advertising, a division of JWT-USA
1984 Senior Vice President, Director of Communications and Development.
1988 Retired from JWT; co-founded Smith Clark Associates, a consulting firm based in Princeton, N.J.
2009 Feb. 4 Died, Princeton, N.J.
Clark served on the Princeton (N.J.) Borough Zoning Board, the Amenia (N.Y.) Zoning Board of Adjustment and the Master Planning Committee; member of the Board of Directors of the McCarter Theatre, Princeton Singers and Trenton Children's Chorus. He was also active in the theater and appeared in several local productions. [Sources: J. Walter Thompson Company Biographical Information; Princeton Town Topics obituary Feb. 18, 2009]
Collection Overview
The Harry Clark Papers cover the years 1945-1992, with the bulk of materials dating from the 1970s, the period during which Clark served as Director of the JWT Frankfurt Office, and during 1984-1986, when he served as Director of JWT in New York. The collection primarily consists of correspondence, administrative forms, presentations, speeches, meeting files, proofs, and financial reports, with extensive records from the Frankfurt Office. The collection also includes agency slide presentations, tear sheets, as well as photographs and other memorabilia of advertising events. Companies represented include Braun, Chevron, De Beers, Eastman Kodak Company, Kellogg Company, Pan American Airways, PepsiCo, Rustenburg Platinum Mines, and Unilever. Correspondence and other items exist in several languages and have not been translated into English.
Collection Arrangement
The collection is arranged into eleven series: General Office Files, Client Files, Correspondence, Frankfurt Office, International Offices, Meetings, New Business, Reports, Writings and Speeches, Audiovisual Materials, and Oversize Materials. General Office Files contain administrative forms, personnel lists, financial records, and other files related primarily to the running of JWT's U.S. offices. Client Files include correspondence, contracts, marketing plans, presentations, and promotional materials relating to domestic and international accounts. Correspondence includes Clark's correspondence with JWT employees, as well as with charitable and other organizations. Frankfurt Office files include client files, correspondence, and new business files relating to Clark's career as Managing Director of the Frankfurt Office, 1970-1973. International Offices files contain correspondence, marketing plans, and other documents related to JWT's international offices. Meetings consist of charts, presentation scripts, memoranda and logistical information, and notes pertaining to various JWT meetings and general advertising events. New Business files contain presentations, plans, meeting files, and marketing plans related to JWT new accounts prospects. Reports consist of annual reports and operations reviews documenting the financial and organizational performance of JWT domestic and international offices. Writings and Speeches include primarily printed texts of speeches given by Clark and other JWT advertising executives. Audiovisual Materials consist of audio cassettes related to the 1984 World Advertising Forum. Oversize Materials include large-format items removed from the previous series.
Related Material
Related materials may be found in the following Hartman Center collections of the J. Walter Thompson Company Archives:
Rena Bartos Papers
Colin Dawkins Papers
Don Johnston Papers
Dan Seymour Papers
Thomas Sutton Papers
Frankfurt Office. George Black Papers
Frankfurt Office. Hans Ihlefeld Papers
Frankfurt Office. Paul-G. Siebel Papers
Advertising agencies -- Germany; Advertising agencies; Advertising executives; Advertising agencies -- United States; Advertising -- Germany -- History -- 20th century; Advertising -- Germany; Advertising -- United States -- History -- 20th century; Advertising -- United States; Clippings (information artifacts); Photographs; Advertising -- Management; Audiocassettes; Braun; Chevron Corporation; Unilever (Firm); Pan American Airways Corporation; Kellogg Company; J. Walter Thompson Company. New York Office; J. Walter Thompson Company; J. Walter Thompson Company; John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History; Clark, Harry (Harold Frank, Jr.), 1935-2009; De Beers Consolidated Mines; Eastman Kodak Company; J. Walter Thompson Company. Frankfurt Office
- General Office Files, 1945-1986, 2 boxes
  Scope and Contents note
  Includes administrative forms, personnel lists, financial records, and other files related primarily to the running of JWT's U.S. offices. Original folder titles were maintained and items were arranged alphabetically.
  - Client-agency evaluations, 1985 (Box 1)
  - Committees, 1974-1975 (Box 1)
  - Effie Awards applications, 1984 (Box 1)
  - Financial papers
    - Consolidated cost data, 1957-1972 (Box 1)
    - International cost data, circa 1958-1971 (Box 1)
    - Monthly assessment summaries, 1975 (Box 1)
    - New York Office
      - Cost data, 1965-1974 (Box 1)
      - Profits and losses, 1965-1980, 2 folders (Box 1)
      - Profits and losses by client, 1975 (Box 1)
    - Profits by client, circa 1945-1964, 1-2 of 3 folders (Box 1)
    - Profits by client, circa 1945-1964 (continued), 3 of 3 folders (Box 2)
    - Profit-sharing trust, 1964, 1969 (Box 2)
  - Formal Reporting Procedures, all offices, 1974 (Box 2)
  - Formal Reporting Requirements
    - Non-U.S. offices, 1976 (Box 2)
    - U.S. offices, 1976 (Box 2)
  - Internal and external communications, 1974-1975 (Box 2)
  - JWT Communications Program, Second Quarter Review, 1975 (Box 2)
  - JWT employees in commercials, 1975 (Box 2)
  - JWT mock résumé, circa 1986 (Box 2)
  - Management news summary, 1984-1987 (Box 2)
  - Media Department personnel, 1975 (Box 2)
  - Metric system, 1975 (Box 2)
  - New York Times Information Bank, 1975 (Box 2)
  - Organization chart, 1975 (Box 2)
  - Outside directors, 1975 (Box 2)
  - Pension Reform Act of 1974, 1975 (Box 2)
  - Strategic Services Department, 1986 (Box 2)
  - U.S. offices
    - Atlanta, 1974 (Box 2)
    - Chicago, 1974-1975 (Box 2)
    - Detroit, 1974 (Box 2)
    - Indianapolis, 1974 (Box 2)
    - Los Angeles, 1974-1975 (Box 2)
    - San Francisco, 1974 (Box 2)
  - 1976 calendar, 1975 (Box 2)
- Client Files, 1961-1987, 6 boxes
  Includes typed and handwritten, correspondence, telexes, notes, contracts, marketing plans, memoranda, presentations, promotional materials, reports, and research concerning the domestic and international accounts with which Clark was involved. Original folder titles were maintained and items were arranged alphabetically by client.
  - General (Box 3)
    - Aligned Client List, 1976 (Box 3)
    - Client costing, 1974 (Box 3)
    - Client evaluation, 1973 (Box 3)
    - Client information search, 1973 (Box 3)
    - Cost Saving, 1987 (Box 3)
    - International clients, Summary of Account Reviews, 1976 (Box 3)
    - Miscellaneous clients, 1975 (Box 3)
    - Multinational clients, 1975 (Box 3)
    - U.S. client booklets, 1974 (Box 3)
  - Alpargatas, 1976 (Box 3)
  - AT&T, 1973 (Box 3)
  - Baker-Beech Nut Corporation
    - General, 1973-1976, 3 folders (Box 3)
    - Happy Meal Times for Your Baby, 1976 (Box 3)
  - Bluebell, 1973, 1976, 2 folders (Box 3)
  - Braun, 1976 (Box 3)
  - British-American Tobacco Co., Ltd., 1976 (Box 3)
  - Brown & Williamson, 1976 (Box 3)
  - Caltex, 1976 (Box 3)
  - Carrier International
    - General, 1974 (Box 3)
    - Summary of agency presentation, 1974 (Box 3)
  - Champion, 1976 (Box 3)
  - Chesebrough-Pond's, 1976 (Box 3)
  - Chevron
    - General, 1976 (Box 3)
    - Draft for a Plans Board document: Chevron of Europe: 1974 Considerations in Case of Gasoline Shortage, 1973 (Box 3)
  - Christian Dior, slides, undated (Box 3)
  - Courvoisier, 1976 (Box 3)
  - De Beers
    - General, 1974-1976, 1-2 of 10 folders (Box 3)
    - General, 1974-1976 (continued), 3-10 of 10 folders (Box 4)
    - Gem Advertising, Publicity and Promotion, Spain, 1974-1975 (Box 4)
    - Gem Diamonds: Marketing Recommendations for 1976, 1975 (Box 5)
    - Gem Diamonds: Marketing Recommendations for 1977, 1976 (Box 5)
    - Gem Diamonds: Proposals for Marketing Large Stones, 1975 (Box 5)
    - 1977 Recommendation for De Beers Consolidated Mines, 1976 (Box 5)
  - Eastman Chemical, 1976 (Box 5)
  - Eastman Kodak
    - General, 1976 (Box 5)
    - International Coordination of the Eastman Kodak Account, 1976 (Box 5)
  - Ford Motor Company, 1976 (Box 5)
  - Foreign Vintage, 1976 (Box 5)
  - Fund America, 1976 (Box 5)
  - Gillette, 1976 (Box 5)
  - Goldman Sachs, 1976 (Box 5)
  - Guinness, 1973-1976 (Box 5)
  - Hallmark, 1976 (Box 5)
  - Hills Bros., 1976 (Box 5)
  - Interbank, 1976 (Box 5)
  - Intercard, 1976 (Box 5)
  - Johnson & Johnson, 1974-1976 (Box 5)
  - Kawasaki, 1976 (Box 5)
  - Kellogg's
    - General, 1976, 2 folders (Box 5)
    - Brochures, 1976 (Box 5)
    - Distribution lists, 1976 (Box 5)
    - [Packaging folder removed to Oversize Materials.] (Box 5)
    - Public Relations Education Program, 1977 (Box 5)
    - Hans Ruter Visit, 1976 (Box 5)
  - Key Biscayne (Box 6)
    - General, 1974-1975 (Box 6)
    - Meeting, 1976 (Box 6)
  - Klaus Jacobs, 1976 (Box 6)
  - Knorr, 1976 (Box 6)
  - Kraft, 1976 (Box 6)
  - Lejaby, 1976 (Box 6)
    [Some items removed to Oversize Materials.]
  - Lever Brothers, Analysis of Lever Brothers' and Competitive Promotions for 1958-1960, 1961 (Box 6)
  - Lyons Maid Ice Cream, 1976 (Box 6)
  - Malaysian Airways, 1976 (Box 6)
  - Mentholatum, 1976 (Box 6)
  - Milupa
    - General, 1976, 2 folders (Box 6)
    - Market Viability of Milupa Infant Food, 1975 (Box 6)
  - Nestlé, 1976 (Box 6)
  - Novamark, 1975-1976 (Box 6)
  - Pan American Airways
    - General, 1976 (Box 6)
    - Ad Kit, 1977 (Box 6)
  - PepsiCo, 1976 (Box 6)
  - RCA, Marketing Concept of Campaign Planning, 1971 (Box 6)
  - Rustenburg Platinum Mines
    - General, 1976, 1-2 of 4 folders (Box 6)
    - General, 1976 (continued), 3-4 of 4 folders (Box 7)
    - Billings, 1976 (Box 7)
    - Matthey Bishop file, 1976 (Box 7)
    - Budget, 1976 (Box 7)
    - Call reports, 1976, 2 folders (Box 7)
    - Creative, 1976 (Box 7)
    - Letter of terms, 1976 (Box 7)
    - Platinum in the U.S., 1976
      - Presentation book (Box 7)
      - Proposal (Box 7)
    - Platinum News, 1976 (Box 7)
    - Presentations, 1976 (Box 7)
    - Reckitt & Colman file, 1976 (Box 8)
    - Retail decisions, 1975-1976 (Box 8)
    - Shearman & Sterling file, 1976 (Box 8)
    - Trip, 1976, 2 folders (Box 8)
  - Schering Plough, 1976 (Box 8)
  - S.C. Johnson, 1976 (Box 8)
  - Schweppes, 1976 (Box 8)
  - Scott, 1976 (Box 8)
  - Seven-Up, 1976 (Box 8)
  - Singer, 1976 (Box 8)
  - Scientifically Treated Petroleum (STP), 1976 (Box 8)
  - Studebaker-Worthington, 1976 (Box 8)
  - Teledyne Water Pik, 1976 (Box 8)
  - Unilever
    - General, 1976, 2 folders (Box 8)
    - JWT Discussion Group, 1975, Nov. 6-7 (Box 8)
  - United States Marine Corps, Communications Plan, 1974 (Box 8)
  - Warner Lambert
    - General, 1976 (Box 8)
    - Presentations, 1987, 2 folders (Box 8)
  - W.F. Young, 1976 (Box 8)
  - Whitehall, 1976 (Box 8)
  - Wimpy's, 1976 (Box 8)
  - Worthington Pump, 1976 (Box 8)
  - Wrangler, 1976 (Box 8)
- Correspondence, 1973-1988, 4 boxes
  Comprised of correspondence primarily between Harry Clark and other JWT employees, as well as Clark's communications with charitable and other organizations. Also contains interoffice communications such as notes, memoranda, and reports, as well as some personal correspondence. Some of the correspondence arrived grouped in Chronological Books ordered by date; these groupings were maintained. Original folder titles were maintained and items were arranged alphabetically.
  - Advertising Research Foundation, 1976 (Box 8)
  - American Marketing Association, 1976 (Box 8)
  - Blood Drive, 1976 (Box 8)
  - Bonus Payments Policy, 1976 (Box 8)
  - Century Lausanne, 1974 (Box 8)
  - Challenges and Responses letter, 1976 (Box 8)
  - Christmas gifts and cards, 1976 (Box 8)
  - Chronological memo file, 1974, 6 folders (Box 9)
  - Chronological memos to all managers, 1975 (Box 9)
  - Client-office assessment list, 1976 (Box 9)
  - Committees, miscellaneous files, 1974 (Box 9)
  - Company policy, 1974 (Box 9)
  - Dentsu Advertising, 1974 (Box 10)
  - Dialog (Public Communications Division of JWT)
    - General, 1974 (Box 10)
    - Assessment letter, 1975 (Box 10)
  - Discovery Center, 1974 (Box 10)
  - European Association of Advertising Agencies, 1974 (Box 10)
  - European Central Services, 1974 (Box 10)
  - Euroscope, 1974 (Box 10)
  - Food Exhibits, 1973 (Box 10)
  - Ken Fraser visits, 1975-1976, 2 folders (Box 10)
    [Includes reports: JWT-Unilever Worldwide Billings, Costs and Profits; Status of Commercial Radio Around the World.]
  - Roger Gould memoranda, 1978 (Box 10)
  - Lou Harris Studies memoranda, 1975 (Box 10)
  - Harvard University, 1975 (Box 10)
  - Jack Hilton, 1975 (Box 10)
  - International Advertising Association, 1974 (Box 10)
  - International art file, 1974 (Box 10)
  - International Marketing and Media (Media Decisions), 1974 (Box 10)
  - JWT Advertising Group, 1976 (Box 10)
  - JWT art collection, 1976 (Box 10)
  - JWT contract, 1974 (Box 10)
  - JWT corporate identity, 1975 (Box 10)
  - Dr. Christopher Lovelock correspondence, 1975 (Box 10)
  - Media Department memos, 1975 (Box 10)
  - Memos to international managers, 1974 (Box 10)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1975 (Box 10)
  - Miscellaneous memoranda, 1973-1974, 1987-1988, 2 folders (Box 11)
  - Nassau Inn, 1975 (Box 11)
  - New York Advertising, 1974 (Box 11)
  - New York Jazz Museum, 1975 (Box 11)
  - Personal correspondence, 1975 (Box 11)
  - Public relations, 1975 (Box 11)
  - Henry Simmons memos, 1975 (Box 11)
  - Staff memos, 1976 (Box 11)
  - Tate & Lyle memos, 1976 (Box 11)
  - Michael Thomas Language Center, 1973-1975 (Box 11)
  - WPP-JWT takeover, 1987 (Box 11)
- Frankfurt Office, 1970-1973, 8 boxes
  Includes material relating to Harry Clark's career at the J. Walter Thompson GmbH advertising agency while he was Managing Director of the Frankfurt, Germany office, 1970-1973. The papers document Clark's work with major clients at JWT's Frankfurt office. The materials primarily concern his work with international clients such as De Beers, Pan American, and Unilever, and provides insight into the close coordination and cooperation among JWT's international offices when working with such clients. The papers consist of correspondence, telexes, memoranda, notes, reports, photoboards, advertisements, photographs, clippings, and printed materials. Clients of the company represented in the collection include Braun, De Beers, Glücksklee, S.C. Johnson, Kellogg, Pan Am, and Unilever. Correspondents include clients such as Burda Du Pont, Eilebrecht, Ford, Maggi, Pan Am, and Wick Pharma; other JWT Offices; and JWT executives including Don Johnston, Peter Durham, and Myron R. May. The majority the collection (approximately 70%) is in English, and the remainder is in German.
  For related material, see the papers of other Frankfurt office executives, Frankfurt print advertisements, and the Frankfurt video collection.
  Processing Note
  The series has been arranged into four subseries: Client files, Correspondence, International offices, and New business. The original organization of the material has been retained in large parts. The only change that was made was to break up the strictly chronological arrangement of all records by business year so that the individual series could be brought together and would cover the entire range of years for which records exist. No documents have been removed. The client names have also been retained according to the filing system of the Frankfurt Office. All newsletters from other JWT Offices have been transferred to the newsletter collection.
  - Client Files
    Documents Clark's day-to-day work for his clients; the development of campaigns and the production of advertisements; campaign presentations; and marketing schemes used by the Frankfurt office. Clark supervised the accounts for Braun, De Beers, Glücksklee, S.C. Johnson, Kellogg, Pan Am, and Unilever. From 1971-1973, the series contains detailed information about JWT Frankfurt's work for these clients. Included is the correspondence with clients, JWT Frankfurt's budget and campaign planning including scripts and layouts, Clark's attendance at client conferences, and his communication with other JWT Offices on behalf of these accounts. The Pan Am files reveal some of the particular German sensitivities in the advertising market (such as the 1972 Luxembourg advertisement). Almost half of this series concerns Clark's work for several Unilever accounts. Under the heading Unilever, insight is provided into his efforts for various Elida Gibbs and Lever-Sunlight products (Elidor, Harmony, Gloria, Es wirkt, Mentadent C, and Pepsodent).
    - Braun
      - Correspondence, 1972-1973, 3 folders (Box 11)
      - Memoranda, 1972-1973 (Box 11)
      - Reports, 1972-1973 (Box 11)
    - De Beers
      - Budget and campaign planning, 1971-1974 (Box 11)
      - Conference papers, 1972-1973 (Box 11)
      - Correspondence, 1971-1974, 5 folders (Box 12)
      - International Gold Corporation, 1972 (Box 12)
      - Memoranda, 1971-1973, 2 folders (Box 12)
    - Glücksklee
      - Call reports, 1971 (Box 12)
      - Correspondence, 1971 (Box 12)
      - Memoranda, 1971 (Box 12)
      - Reports, 1971 (Box 12)
      - Scripts, 1971 (Box 12)
    - Johnson
      - Correspondence,1969-1971, 2 folders (Box 12)
      - Memoranda, 1969-1971 (Box 12)
      - Reports, 1969-1971 (Box 12)
    - Kellogg (Box 13)
      - Brochures and recipes, 1971 (Box 13)
      - Call reports, 1971 (Box 13)
      - Conferences, 1971-1972 (Box 13)
      - Correspondence, 1971
        - Germany (Box 13)
        - International (Box 13)
        - Other JWT offices (Box 13)
      - Memoranda, 1971 (Box 13)
      - Public relations correspondence, 1970-1971 (Box 13)
      - Scripts and Layouts, 1971 (Box 13)
      - Reports, 1971 (Box 13)
    - Pan American Airways
      - Advertising texts, 1973 (Box 13)
      - Campaign (Luxemburg ad), 1972 (Box 13)
      - Campaign planning, 1972-1973, (2 folders) (Box 13)
      - Correspondence
        - General, 1972-1973, 2 folders (Box 13)
        - Other JWT offices, 1971-1973, 1-2 of 3 folders (Box 13)
        - Other JWT offices, 1971-1973 (continued), 3 of 3 folders (Box 14)
      - Memoranda, 1971-1973 (Box 14)
      - Meeting, 1972 (Box 14)
    - Unilever
      - Central media buying, 1973 (Box 14)
      - Conferences, 1972-1973, 2 folders (Box 14)
      - Correspondence, 1972, 2 folders (Box 14)
      - Memoranda, 1972 (Box 14)
    - Unilever (Elida Gibbs)
      - Correspondence, 1972-1973, 3 folders (Box 14)
      - Es Wirkt, 1973 (Box 14)
      - Hair preparations
        - Call reports, 1971 (Box 14)
        - Campaign planning, 1972-1973, 3 folders (Box 14)
        - Conference, 1971 (Box 15)
        - Correspondence, 1971, 2 folders (Box 15)
        - Memoranda, 1971 (Box 15)
        - Reports, 1971 (Box 15)
        - Scripts, 1971 (Box 15)
      - Memoranda, 1973 (Box 15)
      - Mentadent C
        - Correspondence, 1973, 2 folders (Box 15)
        - Memoranda, 1972-1973, 2 folders (Box 15)
      - Pepsodent
        - Call reports, 1971 (Box 15)
        - Correspondence, 1971, 2 folders (Box 15)
        - Memoranda, 1971 (Box 15)
        - Scripts and layouts, 1970-1971 (Box 15)
    - Unilever (Lever-Sunlicht)
      - Campaign planning, 1973 (Box 15)
      - Correspondence, 1972-1973, 2 folders (Box 15)
  - Correspondence
    Consists of both internal and external correspondence. The internal correspondence documents the flow of information from the executive level to the staff level (Haus-Mitteilungen), and provides insight into the daily operations in the Frankfurt Office. Frankfurt's internal communication discusses contacts with clients and the preparation of campaign presentations, conferences, market research, new policies on billings, advertising regulations, staff appointments, and news from other JWT offices. The external correspondence documents the communication with several clients including Burda, Du Pont, Eilebrecht, Ford, Maggi, Pan Am, Rivella International, Savon Gayal, Vereinigte Papierwerke, Wick Pharma as well as an exchange of information with other JWT offices concerning clients, new business, and international markets. The correspondence with Don Johnston consists of a collection of Johnston's memoranda to JWT International Office Managers concerning the planning for the year ahead, appointments, inquiries and information about international clients as well as some direct correspondence between Clark and Johnston.
    - Allgemein
      - General, 1970, 1-3 of 5 folders (Box 15)
      - General, 1970 (continued), 4-5 of 5 folders (Box 16)
      - External, 1971-1973, 5 folders (Box 16)